Wilton Historical Society Photograph Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- 1. Houses
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - 379 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 779)
    - 383 Hurlbutt Street - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 778)
    - 434 Hurlbutt Street - Sturges family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 116)
    - Hurlbutt Street - Houses, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 158)
    - Intersection of Mountain Road and Route 7 in Georgetown, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 101)
    - Keiser family house, farm, and fields, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 103)
    - 7 Kensett Avenue - Rock family house, 1930 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 805)
    - Knob Crook Glen, Georgetown, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 112)
    - 3 Liberty Street - Barrett family house, 1995 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 966)
    - Lockwood family house, undated; File includes postcard of artist's house. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 189)
    - 19 Lovers Lane - Olmstead-Merwin family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 204)
    - 26 Lovers Lane - Merwin family house, 1820 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 802)
    - 3 Millstone Road - House, 1966 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 668)
    - 120 Millstone Road - Searles-Findorak family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 853)
    - 166 Millstone Road - Rimer family house, 1870 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 814)
    - 296 Millstone Road - Whitlock family house, 1890 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 394)
    - 42 Mountain Road - Lockwood family house, 1930; File includes a postcard. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 955)
    - 175 Mountain Road - Keeler family house, 1920s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 74)
    - New York - Rockwell family homestead, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 736)
    - Newtown Road - Betts family house and blacksmith, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 299)
    - 1 Nod Hill Road - Weir family house, circa 1900; This house is located in Ridgefield. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 125)
    - 88 Nod Hill Road - Barrett family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 875)
    - 108 Nod Hill Road - Hubbard family house, 1966 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 667)
    - 162 Nod Hill Road - Lamont family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 190)
    - 184 Nod Hill Road - House, 1929 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 70)
    - 200 Nod Hill Road - Sperry family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 798)
    - 269 Nod Hill Road - Lawrence family house, 1973 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 94)
    - 289 Nod Hill Road - Morgan family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 272)
    - 314 Nod Hill Road - Scribner-St. John family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 749)
    - 430 Nod Hill Road - Olmstead family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 746)
    - 430 Nod Hill Road -Slaughter family house, 1970 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 953)
    - 464 Nod Hill Road - Breed family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 801)
    - 518 Nod Hill Road - Kreger family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 244)
    - 518 Nod Hill Road - Olmstead family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 48)
    - 597 Nod Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 889)
    - 610 Nod Hill Road - DeForest family house, circa 1890 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 877)
    - 735 Nod Hill Road - Weir family house, 1989 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 886)
    - Nod Hill Road - Van Hoosear family house, 1921 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 270)
    - North Main and Church Street, Georgetown - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 242)
    - 49 Old Danbury Road - Jenks family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 456)
    - Old Danbury Road - Bradley family house, circa 1911 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 910)
    - 35 Old Forge Road - Meek family house, 1997 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 845)
    - 200 Old Huckleberry Hill Road - Moriarity family house, 1955 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 78)
    - 146 Old Kings Highway - Vion family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 942)
    - Old Mill Road, Georgetown - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 215)
    - 126 Old Ridgefield Road - Ethel Hart house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 874)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - Gorham family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 675)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 100)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - Jackson family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 642)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - Schenck family house, 1897 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 589)
    - Old Ridgefield Road - T. Miller house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 928)
    - 122 Olmstead Hill Road - Foster family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 198)
    - 147 Olmstead Hill Road - Olmstead family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 126)
    - 190 Olmstead Hill Road - Street-Black family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 147)
    - 236 Olmstead Hill Road - Olmstead family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 114)
    - Olmstead Hill - House, undated; Shows house site only. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 200)
    - Out houses, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 929)
    - Pimpewaug Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 459)
    - 67 Pine Ridge Road - Workman family house, circa 1930 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 821)
    - 9 Poplar Plain Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 519)
    - 270 Range Road - Heller family house, circa 1940 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 75)
    - 27 Redding Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 732)
    - 29 Redding Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 880)
    - 65 Ridgefield Road - Sturges family house / parsonage, 1894 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 203)
    - 67 Ridgefield Road - Fancher-Moir-Duke family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 211)
    - 77 Ridgefield Road - Comstock-Dana family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 162)
    - 80 Ridgefield Road - Winton family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 883)
    - 108 Ridgefield Road - Davenport family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 266)
    - 122 Ridgefield Road - Jessup family house, 1920 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 708)
    - 183 Ridgefield Road - Schlichting family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 697)
    - 211 Ridgefield Road - Thomson / Thompson house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 610)
    - 242 Ridgefield Road - Ogden-Goetz-King family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 240)
    - 274 Ridgefield Road - Middlebrook family house, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 491)
    - 300 Ridgefield Road - Middlebrook family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 745)
    - 358 Ridgefield Road - Rockwell family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 743)
    - 367 Ridgefield Road - Marvin family house and tavern, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 367)
    - 384 Ridgefield Road - Olmstead family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 750)
    - 408 Ridgefield Road - Kumpf family house and bird barn, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 296)
    - 422 Ridgefield Road - Ressequie family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 196)
    - 433 Ridgefield Road - Comstock family house, 1911 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 406)
    - 512 Ridgefield Road - Lyons-Conrad family house, 1888 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 284)
    - 522 Ridgefield Road - Wescott-Prins family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 221)
    - 605 Ridgefield Road - DeWitt family house, 1893 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 707)
    - 635 Ridgefield Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 565)
    - 652 Ridgefield Road - Keeler family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 265)
    - 716 Ridgefield Road - Morgan family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 264)
    - 735 Ridgefield Road - Ayers family house, 1975 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 259)
    - 742 Ridgefield Road - Keeler family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 263)
    - 752 Ridgefield Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 311)
    - 792 Ridgefield Road - Degener family house, 1990 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 894, 895)
    - 807 Ridgefield Road - Patchen family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 751)
    - 808 Ridgefield Road - Howard-Camp family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 176)
    - 846 Ridgefield Road - St. John family house, 1826 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 248)
    - 860 Ridgefield Road - Morgan family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 262)
    - 1042 Ridgefield Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 815)
    - 1090 Ridgefield Road - Hubbard family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 710)
    - Ridgefield Road - Houses and buildings, 1930 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 69, 860)
    - Ridgefield Road - Murphy family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 604)
    - Ridgefield Road, Wilton Center, 1977 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 415)
    - 114 Ruscoe Road - Middlebrook family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 223)
    - 103 Scribner Hill Road - Betts family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 742)
    - 125 Scribner Hill Road - Youngquist family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 629)
    - 36 Seeley Road - Hurlbutt-Tunnel family house, 1902 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 234)
    - 51 Shadow Lane - Abbott family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 882)
    - Shadow Lane - Houses, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 161)
    - 43 Sharp Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 615)
    - 171 Sharp Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 734)
    - 206 Sharp Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 111)
    - 208 Sharp Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 108)
    - 224 Sharp Hill Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 104)
    - 240 Sharp Hill Road - Abbott family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 115)
    - Sharp Hill - Houses, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 210)
    - Sharp Hill Road - Bedient family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 209)
    - 105 Skunk Lane - Wilcek family house, 1936 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 143)
    - Skunk Lane - Wilcek family house, 1940s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 46)
    - 18 Spoonwood Road - Camm family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 701)
    - 6 Station Road - Burlock family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 384)
    - 88 Sturges Ridge Road - Sturges family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 752)
    - 109 Sturges Ridge Road - C. Jackson house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 855)
    - 137 Sturges Ridge Road - Davidson family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 558)
    - 167 Sturges Ridge Road - Jackson family house, 1928 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 915)
    - 214 Sturges Ridge Road - House, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 917)
    - Thomson / Thompson - House interior, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 430)
    - Unidentified houses, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 275)
    - 11 Wampum Hill - Sturges family house, 1950 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 102)
    - West Church Street - Bennett family house - Christmas cards, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 958)
    - West Church Street - Fred Sturges house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 307)
    - Weston - Silliman-Andrews family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 279)
    - 155 Whipstick Road - St. John family house, 1888 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 197)
    - Wilton Center - Davis family house, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 866)
- 2. People and families
  - Photographs in boxes
    - Unidentified family group of thirteen people, circa 1890; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 2)
    - Elderly woman and child with teddy bear, undated; This photograph was part of a 1995 exhibit. (Box P-OS-3, Item 7)
    - Gilbert, Edward O. with Belden Hill Milk Dairy cart and horse, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 7)
    - Monroe, Henry and the last Wilton blacksmith shop, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 10)
    - Funeral of servant of Joseph Hurlbutt family, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 16)
    - Barrett, William and Hurlbutt Street General Store, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 17)
    - Merwin, Tim and Gus, undated; Photograph is unmatted. (Box P-OS-1, Item 20)
    - Merwin, Timothy fishing, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 28)
    - Weir, J. Alden at his farm, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 29)
    - Marshall, Eleanor Chapin - Wedding photograph, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 30)
    - “She was a good woman,” funeral of a servant, undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 33)
    - St. John, William "Uncle Billy", undated; This photograph was part of the Wilton Library Bicentennial Exhibit, "Wilton Then," in 2002. (Box P-OS-2, Item 37)
  - Photographs in file cabinets
    - Thompson, Katherine, 1922 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 8)
    - Meyer family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 24)
    - Wilton Center Stationmaster, 1935 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 29)
    - St. John, William "Uncle Billy", undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 288)
    - Marhoffer family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 304)
    - Adams, Charles, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 308)
    - Bassett, Samuel and Thomas, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 309)
    - Little family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 315)
    - Belden family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 318)
    - Betts family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 319)
    - Bennett family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 320)
    - Bloomer, Harold, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 322)
    - Cannon, Charles, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 323)
    - Comstock family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 324)
    - Ambler family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 325)
    - Ambler, Charles Meeker, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 327)
    - Ambler, Elizabeth "Betty" Raymond - Wedding, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 328)
    - Canfield family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 330)
    - Davenport family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 331)
    - Carvutto family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 332)
    - Disbrow family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 333)
    - Fillow, Walter, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 335)
    - Gilbert, Edwin, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 336)
    - Gregory family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 337)
    - Hart family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 340)
    - Ambler, Elizabeth "Betty" Raymond - Horse Show, 1968 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 341)
    - Hubbell family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 344)
    - Jackson family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 345)
    - Keeler, Robert W. and Ruth Zelda (Raymond), undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 348)
    - Keeler, Alice Ruth, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 350)
    - Keeler, Elizabeth "Bessie" Louise, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 351)
    - Keeler, Katherine, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 352)
    - Keeler, William, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 353)
    - Lockwood family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 354)
    - Lyon, Louise, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 355)
    - Middlebrook family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 357)
    - Morgan family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 360)
    - Ogden, George, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 362)
    - Olmstead family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 369)
    - Sturges, Donald, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 371)
    - Sturges family sisters, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 372)
    - Sturges, Dr. Fred, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 373)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 374)
    - Rowland family, 1906 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 375)
    - Schlicting, Frank, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 376)
    - Sterling family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 377)
    - Sturges, John Burr, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 378)
    - Sturges, Samuel B., undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 379)
    - Thayer, Sarah and family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 380)
    - Tonguin, "Black" Jack, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 381)
    - Sturges, Fred - Family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 382)
    - Van Hoosear, David Hermon, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 383)
    - Merwin family, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 386)
    - Miller family, circa 1904 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 387)
    - Crofut, Inez, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 388)
    - Wilton children at party, 1903 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 389)
    - Van Hoosear, C. - Mailman - With horse and wagon, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 393)
    - Godfrey family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 407)
    - Hollister family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 409)
    - Hallock family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 410)
    - Fisher, Rev. Samuel, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 423)
    - Post family, undated; See also photographs of the Hurlbutt Street schoolhouse. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 426)
    - Dana, Charles, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 428)
    - White, Mrs. Charles, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 429)
    - Purple, Edson, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 431)
    - Jackson, Harry, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 432)
    - Irvine, Olive Kennedy, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 433)
    - Van Wyck, Phillip - Family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 435)
    - Middlebrook, Lillian, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 440)
    - Richards family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 446)
    - Fitch, Joseph Platt, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 477)
    - Fitch, Sherman Platt, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 478)
    - Fitch, Sarah Maria (Jones), 1790 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 479)
    - Marvin, Matthew - Former home in Essex, England, undated; The house is the one from which he emigrated. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 560)
    - Meeker, Ezra, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 492)
    - Winton family, 1907 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 499)
    - Raymond, Clarisa, 1918 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 501)
    - Lambert, David Rogers, 1905 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 505)
    - Lambert, Samuel F., 1941 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 506)
    - Lambert, David S. R., undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 532)
    - Leatherman, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 533)
    - Gorham, John, 1965 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 563)
    - Roberts, Robert, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 567)
    - Lambert, Eva Ogden, circa 1900 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 569)
    - Crofut, Bill - Musician, circa 1958 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 570)
    - Dewing family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 571)
    - Portraits - Unidentified, 1943 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 591)
    - Family snapshots - Unidentified, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 592)
    - Thayer, Stephen and family, 1925 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 595)
    - Middlebrook, James and family, 1924 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 596)
    - Thayer, Grace Zelma, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 597)
    - Fitch family reunion, 1980 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 600)
    - Bethel, Mary Ann Nichols, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 609)
    - Bethel, Claudine M., undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 611)
    - Bethel, Maud, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 612)
    - Bethel family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 613)
    - Steichen, Kate Rodina, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 620)
    - Rev. Hooker, 1987 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 631)
    - Grumman, Seth with horse and buggy, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 635)
    - Ogden, F. Clerc, 1894 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 640)
    - Hurlbutt, David, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 646)
    - Hurlbutt, Lewis, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 647)
    - Hurlbutt, Josephine, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 648)
    - Partrick family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 650)
    - Gregory, Julian Sr., undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 659)
    - Squires, Mac - Artist, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 663)
    - Hubbard, G. Evans - Family, circa 1944 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 664)
    - Merwin, Gus Jr., at Norwalk River, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 685)
    - Merwin, T. with horse and cart, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 691)
    - DeWitt family, 1893 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 706)
    - Schenck family, 1923 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 709)
    - Merwin family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 716)
    - Bethel, Mary Ann Nichols and family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 718)
    - Fitch family members, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 728)
    - Hurd, Frances, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 756)
    - Middlebrook, Sarah - Birthday, 1924 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 791)
    - Silverberg, Carol, 1982 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 792)
    - Hart, Ethel, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 794)
    - Jayne brothers, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 795)
    - Haight, Sylvanus, undated; Contains a silhouette portrait. (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 803)
    - Rock, Isabel and family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 804)
    - Andrews family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 806)
    - Blackmar, Dana, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 808)
    - Funeral of a Hurlbutt family servant, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 812)
    - Russell, Mary in First World War uniform, 1942 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 816)
    - Chapin family - Wedding, 1918 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 824)
    - Hurlbutt, Nelson, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 830)
    - Goetjen family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 839)
    - Jackson, Clarence, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 847)
    - Eakland, Alice, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 850)
    - Grumman family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 851)
    - Young family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 852)
    - Stannard-Marhoffer - Wedding, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 865)
    - Piersall family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 869)
    - Carpenter, Anna, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 871)
    - Hurlbutt, Henrietta Sackman, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 885)
    - Sackman family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 898)
    - Ruth, Babe and friends, 1936 (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 907)
    - Warncke family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 918)
    - Ambler, Elizabeth "Betty" Raymond, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 920)
    - Coley, William, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 922)
    - Barringer, George, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 923)
    - Smith, W. and E. Stannard, 1970s (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 931)
    - Slaughter, Eugenia, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 954)
    - Sturges, John Burr, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 956)
    - Sturges family - Photograph album, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 964)
    - Borglum family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 969)
    - Seymour family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 151, 152)
    - Knapp family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 175, 321)
    - Bedient family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 310, 317)
    - Hurlbutt family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 346, 649, 661)
    - Keeler family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 347, 349)
    - Ogden family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 363, 364)
    - DeForest family, undated (Box Cabinet: 6, Folder 896, 971)
- 3. Photograph albums and scrapbooks
  - Albums and scrapbooks in boxes
    - Ambler family, 1900s; This is collection of loose snapshots. It is filed out of order in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. (Box 65, Item 65)
    - Ambler family, 1880s; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. The original Wilton Historical Society accession number for this item is 98.12.255. (Box 71, Item 71)
    - Ambler family, 1896; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. The original Wilton Historical Society accession number for this item is 98.12.258. (Box 72, Item 72)
    - Ambler family, 1893; This is scrapbook of newspaper clippings, including several advertisements for travel. It likely belonged to Elizabeth Raymond. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. (Box 73, Item 73)
    - Ambler family, 1871; This is a scrapbook of newspaper clippings, including ones about local churches and motherhood. It likely belonged to Hannah Raymond Ambler. It is stored in a box and shelved with the bulk of the Ambler collection. (Box 74, Item 74)